webtexts.com 2014-06-23

# User Resources - Privacy Notice - Soomo Publishing

Your privacy is important to us and we value your trust. Please read the following statement of our intentions and commitments to our users regarding personal information. If you need to contact us regarding this policy or our use of your personal information, please call or write to us. Soomo Publishing 9 Pack Square SW, Suite 301 Asheville, NC 28801 (888) 834-7223 [info@soomopublishing.com](mailto:info@soomopublishing.com)

###   
Personal Information We Collect and Why

Instructors:

  * Name - This allows your students to correctly identify you in a list of courses offered.
  * Email address and password - Your personal credentials to sign in to our site.

Students:

  * Name - This allows your instructor to identify you in the class roster.
  * Email address and password - Your personal credentials to sign in to our site.
  * Credit card - For purchase, we collect credit card and billing address information. Our secure form communicates directly with our credit card authorizing service. Your information is not stored on our servers.

We will not sell or share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties. 

###   
How We Use Your Personal Information

  * Your email address and password will be used to identify you as an authorized user of our services.
  * Your email address may be used to send your password upon request or to communicate with you about access to your course.
  * The contact and financial information you provide when you purchase a subscription will be used to complete that order.
  * We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires.

###   
Anonymous Information

We use non-identifying information to better design our service and to share with third parties for the purposes of product development, research, or statistical analysis. This is information which does not personally and specifically identify you but is derived from your use of our site.

###   
Log Files

We use IP addresses (an identifier for computers on the Internet) to analyze trends, administer the site, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and comply with applicable laws. IP addresses are not linked directly to personally identifiable information. 

###   
Cookies

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer to maintain an uninterrupted transaction with our services. Usage of a cookie by our website is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you will not be able to use our web-based services. 

###   
Legal Disclosure of Information

Soomo Publishing may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Soomo Publishing; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Soomo Publishing. 

###   
Links

Our website contains links to other sites. Soomo Publishing is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

###   
Children Under 13

We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our website, and so we carry out the same privacy policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided us with personally identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

###   
Notification of Changes

Soomo Publishing reserves the right at any time to modify any of our policies. We will post a notice of any changes on our website. As a result, you will always be aware of what information we collect, why we collect the information, and how we use the information. 

###   
Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe. 

###   
How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [info@soomopublishing.com](mailto:info@soomopublishing.com). 

###   
Payment & Refunds

A valid credit card or publisher-provided passkey is required for paying accounts. Free accounts are not required to provide a credit card number. Refunds are available for up to 60 days from the date of purchase. Beyond 60 days, the service is not refundable. Cancellation of your account may result in the loss of work saved. Soomo Publishing does not accept any liability for such loss.
